Howard Mui

Tel: (+852) 9263-0122

Email: howardmui.2020@gmail.com

Website: https://howard-resume-app.firebaseapp.com

Summary

A detail-oriented and self-motivated Digital Operation Centre Engineer with almost one year of experience in providing virtual banks with professional technical support. Having immersed myself in learning programming languages for more than one year, web developing is one of my specialties, the frontend and back-end required languages in particular. In possession of problem-solving and collaboration skills, the sensitivity of coding has also been nurtured.

Technical Skills

Programming Languages: Html, Css, Javascript, React.js, React Native, Node.js

Database and Continuous Integration: MongoDB, Firebase, Travis CI

Softwares: Git, Sourcetree, Xcode, Android Studio, Adobe(Illustrator, Experience Design), Microsoft Office

Working Experience

Digital Operation Center Engineer

August 2021- April 2022

Resolve Technology Limited

- Monitor the entire operation of virtual banks, including networks, performances of platforms and IT services
- Perform patch management tasks for different console via AWS EC2
- Execute problem-shooting to review the error log via Rancher and Graylog
- Conduct, merge and deploy change task via AWS and CyberArt

Mr. Wu Chi Wai Legislative Councillor Assistant

September 2019 – December 2020

Wu Chi Wai Legislative Councillor

- Created a promotion website through HTML, CSS, JavaScript during the election campaign
- Conducted administrative tasks, followed up with help-seeking cases and managed the social networking accounts
- Designed promotion materials, including leaflets, flyers and posters
- Arranged meetings with help-seekers

Education

Bachelor of Social Sciences (Honours) In Social Policy	2017 - 2019
Hong Kong Baptist University	
Associate of Business Administration in Marketing	2015 - 2017
Community College of City University	
Secondary Graduation	2009 - 2015
Kowloon Tong School (Secondary Section)	
Language	
Proficient in Cantonese, good in English, basic skill in Mandarin	
Expected Salary	
\$19,000 (Negotiable)	
Availability	
Immediately	